const quizzes = [
    {
        question: "What is the most painful ?",
        answer_0: "Hurting your knee",
        answer_1: "Have your heart broken",
        answer_2: "get an F on this exam",
        answer_3: "Sit on a cactus",
        indexOfRightAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Why is it fun to code?",
        answer_0: "Because else i cant communicate",
        answer_1: "It's the cure and the cause to life",
        answer_2: "42",
        answer_3: "redBuLLL",
        indexOfRightAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is a thought? ",
        answer_0: "old you",
        answer_1: "new you",
        answer_2: "another you",
        answer_3: "electric signal a human can compile",
        indexOfRightAnswer: 3
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "What is SonicPi ? ",
        answer_0: "false",
        answer_1: "true",
        answer_2: "denoting 3,14",
        answer_3: "Instrument to program music",
        indexOfRightAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "In HTTP what is 5xx ? ",
        answer_0: "Server error",
        answer_1: "A website",
        answer_2: "Redirection",
        answer_3: "Ghosting",
        indexOfRightAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What is 1+1",
        answer_0: "11",
        answer_1: "2",
        answer_2: "Life",
        answer_3: "Math",
        indexOfRightAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "XSS stands for ? ",
        answer_0: "extra small small",
        answer_1: "true",
        answer_2: "X security signal",
        answer_3: "Cross-Site Scripting",
        indexOfRightAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is React ?",
        answer_0: "opposite of unReact",
        answer_1: "JavaScript Library",
        answer_2: "3,14",
        answer_3: "Facebook",
        indexOfRightAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is SonicPi ? ",
        answer_0: "false",
        answer_1: "true",
        answer_2: "denoting 3,14",
        answer_3: "Instrument to program music",
        indexOfRightAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is SonicPi ? ",
        answer_0: "false",
        answer_1: "true",
        answer_2: "denoting 3,14",
        answer_3: "Instrument to program music",
        indexOfRightAnswer: 3
    }
];


module.exports = {quizzes};